Guide to the Vice President for Student Affairs records, 1923-[ongoing] UA.09.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions A93-37, A93-41, A93-49, 11
  - Duke Debate Endowment Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 151)
  - The Duke Endowment, 1973-1990; 2 folders (Box 152)
  - Duke Endowment Scholarship Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 152)
  - Duke Humanities Review, 1980-1983 (Box 152)
  - Duke Network, 1980-1990 (Box 152)
  - Duke Players, 1978-1986 (Box 152)
  - Duke Vision (1 of 3), 1988-1991 June (Box 152)
  - Duke Vision (2-3 of 3), 1988-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 153)
  - Durham Companions, 1982-1986 (Box 153)
  - East Campus Council, 1986-1990 August (Box 153)
  - East Campus Facilities, 1970-1991 March (Box 153)
  - Emergencies To D.U. Students: Procedures (death, Illness), 1973- 1991 June (Box 153)
  - Emergency Room Guidelines, 1983-1987 (Box 153)
  - Energy Conservation, 1977-1983 (Box 153)
  - Engineering, School Of, 1982-1990 (Box 153)
  - Engineering Student Government, 1978-1991 May (Box 154)
  - ECOS Organization: Environmentally Concerned Organ [sic] Students, 1971- 1991 March (Box 154)
  - Equal Opportunity, Office of, 1970-1990 December (Box 154)
  - Ethics/values, 1987-1991 June (Box 154)
  - Faculty And Staff Members, 1970 December-1991 (Box 154)
  - Financial Aid Correspondence, 1991-1990 June (Box 154)
  - Financial Aid Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 199)
  - Fraternities General Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 154)
  - Fraternities: General Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1983-1990 September (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Phi Omega, 1971-1990 November (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Alpha Tau Omega, 1978-1991 February (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Beta Phi Zeta (1 of 3), 1982-1989 September (Box 201)
  - Fraternities: Beta Phi Zeta (2-3 of 3), 1982-1989; 2 folders (Box 202)
  - Fraternities: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1982 May-1990 August (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Delta Tau Delta, 1981-1990 August (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Alpha, 1981-1990 October (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Alpha Psi, 1983-1990 March (Box 155)
  - Fraternities: Kappa Sigma, 1982-1988 (Box 199)
  - Fraternities: Omega Psi Phi, 1985-1986 (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Phi Delta Theta, 1986-1990 October (Box 199)
    FERPA restricted until 2060.
  - Fraternities: Pi Kappa Phi, 1982-1991 February (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Pi Kappa Psi, 1986-1991 April (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Pi Kappa Sigma, 1982-1990 April (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Pi Kappa Alpha, 1981-1988 (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Psi Upsilon, 1981-1988 (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1981-1991 February (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, 1981-1991 (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Nu, 1982-1991 March (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1981-1991 January (Box 199)
  - Fraternities: Theta Chi, 1983-1990 October (Box 156)
  - Fraternities: Miscellaneous, Groups, 1981 January-1991 March (Box 156)
  - Freewater Cinema Committee, 1981-1990 December (Box 156)
  - Freshman Advisory Council, 1971-1990 (Box 156)
  - Freshman Office, 1969-1990 (Box 156)
  - Freshman Presidents, Council of, 1990 (Box 156)
  - Freshman Survey, circa 1990 (Box 156)
  - Freshman Year Task Force, 1990 (Box 156)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1988-1989 (Box 156)
  - Green House, 1991 (Box 156)
  - Griffith Endowment Fund, 1991 (Box 156)
  - Habitat For Humanity, 1988-1990 (Box 156)
  - Handicapped Committee, 1972-1991; 2 folders (Box 157)
  - Handicapped Persons, Task Force On Regulations Regarding, 1977 (Box 157)
  - Health Professions Advising Office, 1971-1985 (Box 157)
  - Homecoming, 1980-1984 (Box 157)
  - Hoof & Horn, 1982-1991; 2 folders (Box 157)
  - Honor Council, 1982-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 157)
  - Honor Societies, 1979-1990 (Box 158)
  - Housing, 1981-1991; 3 folders (Box 158)
  - Housing: Student Problems, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 158)
  - Housing: Student Problems, 1978-1990 (Box 199)
  - Housing: Management, Office of, 1986-1991; 3 folders (Box 159)
  - Housing (1-2 of 4), 1981-1992; 2 folders (Box 159)
  - Housing (3-4 of 4), 1981-1992; 2 folders (Box 160)
  - Human Resources, 1981 April-1991 June (Box 160)
  - Human Resources: Job Enhancement Program, 1985-1990 (Box 160)
  - Human Resources: Job Family Material, 1979-1983 (Box 160)
  - Human Resources: Student Employment, 1981-1991 (Box 160)
  - Infirmary, 1971-1989 (Box 160)
  - Information Desk Bryan Center, 1981-1990 (Box 161)
  - International Association, 1981-1990 (Box 161)
  - International Studies, Center for, 1983-1990 (Box 161)
  - Inter-view, 1982-1983 (Box 161)
  - IRS Policy On Political Campaigns, 1972 (Box 161)
  - Islamic Association, 1979-1982 (Box 161)
  - Jabberwocky, 1980 December-1989 December (Box 161)
  - Center For Jewish Life: Dir. Of Development, 1990 March-1990 October (Box 161)
  - Center For Jewish Life: Board of Directors, 1990 July-1991 June (Box 161)
  - Center For Jewish Life: Gilbert and Ruth Scharf Fund: Treasurer's Report, 1991 May- (Box 161)
  - Job Opportunities, 1988 April-1991 April (Box 161)
  - Karamu, 1980 January-1991 January (Box 161)
  - Karamu, 1989 (Box 199)
  - Lars Lyon Memorial Award, 1985 July-1991 June (Box 162)
  - Latent Image, 1975 January-1984 March (Box 162)
  - Law School, 1989-1990 November (Box 162)
  - Leadership Program, 1987-1989 (Box 162)
  - Library, 1976 June-1991 January (Box 162)
  - Magnolia Group, 1982-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 162)
  - Mail & Package Delivery, 1987 October-1991 April (Box 163)
  - Material Support Department, 1984-1991 June (Box 163)
  - Media Study: Ad Hoc Committee On Undergraduate Media, 1981 December-1984 May (Box 163)
  - Minority Affairs, 1986-1991 June (Box 163)
  - Modern Black Mass Choir, 1978 November-1990 November (Box 163)
  - Motels/hotels, 1986 March-1990 June (Box 163)
  - Multi-culturalism Task Force, 1989 September-1990 December (Box 163)
  - Music Miscellaneous, 1986 January-1991 June (Box 163)
  - NABSEA (National Association Of Black Students For Education Adv.) (1 of 2), 1987 November-1991 June (Box 163)
  - NABSEA (National Association Of Black Students For Education Adv.) (2 of 2), 1987 November-1991 June (Box 164)
  - NABSEA (National Association Of Black Students For Education Adv.), 1989-1990 (Box 200)
  - NASPA (National Association of Student Personnel Administrators), 1970 March-1990 June (Box 164)
  - National Endowment For The Arts, 1978 February-1991 June (Box 164)
  - National On-Campus Report, 1989 (Box 164)
  - Naylor, Thomas, 1990 September (Box 164)
  - Noise, Conduct, Destructive Behavior, 1979 December-1989 May (Box 164)
  - Notary Publics, 1981 December-1984 August (Box 164)
  - Martin Luther King Birthday Celebration, 1985 Janaury-1991 January (Box 164)
  - Overenrollment Task force, 1986 July-1991 February (Box 164)
  - Page Auditorium, 1986 August-1991 April (Box 164)
  - Parents Weekend, 1981 February-1990 November (Box 165)
  - Part-time Students, 1987 April-1991 February (Box 165)
  - Part-time Students, 1988-1991 (Box 200)
  - President's Suggestion Box, 1987 January-1990 January (Box 165)
  - Project Build, 1989 February-1992 June; 2 folders (Box 165)
  - Public Safety Traffic, 1981-1991 June (Box 165)
  - Public Safety Office, 1986-1991 June (Box 165)
  - Public Safety Office, 1986, 1989 (Box 200)
  - Rape/Assault Awareness (1 of 2), 1987-1991 June (Box 165)
  - Rape/Assault Awareness (2 of 2), 1987-1991 June (Box 166)
  - Rape Education, 1987-1988 (Box 166)
  - Reggie Howard Scholarship, 1976-1991 June (Box 166)
  - Residential Life: Damage In Residence Halls, 1986-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 166)
  - Residential Life/College Planning Taskforce, 1984 August-1987 August; 2 folders (Box 167)
  - Richard Whitted Institute For Minority Students, 1987 June-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 167)
  - Search Committee: Guidelines, 1975 December (Box 167)
  - Senior Class Representatives, 1983 January-1987 February (Box 167)
  - Senior Leadership Award (1-2 of 3), 1981 May-1991 January; 2 folders (Box 167)
  - Senior Leadership Award (3 of 3), 1981 May-1991 January (Box 168)
  - Senior Class Representatives, 1983-1987 (Box 168)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1983-1990 December (Box 168)
    Primarily relates to language prohibiting discrimination based on "sexual preference".
  - Sexism, Racism & Harassment, 1987-1991 June; 4 folders (Box 168)
  - Sexual Harassment: Policy Re, 1980-1987; 2 folders (Box 169)
  - Safety/Security On Campus, 1989 July-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 169)
  - Safety/Security On Campus, 1990 (Box 200)
  - Shoplifting: Policy, 1982 February-1983 January (Box 169)
  - Social Climate On Campus, 1991 February-1991 June (Box 169)
  - Sororities, 1983-1991 June (Box 169)
  - Sororities, 1989-1990 (Box 200)
  - Southern Association Of Colleges & Schools, 1986 October-1990 October (Box 169)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office Of, 1985 June-1991 April
  - Sports Clubs, 1986 January-1991 February (Box 170)
  - Sports Medicine Oversight Committee, 1983-1991 (Box 200)
  - Stag Films, Strippers Policy, 1980 February-1982 July (Box 170)
  - Student Accident & Sickness Policy, 1978-1983 (Box 170)
  - Student Activities, 1986-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 170)
  - Student Emergencies: Accidents, Illness, Etc., 1986-1991 June (Box 200)
  - Student Guide To Duke, 1986-1991 June (Box 170)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee, 1981 February-1986 April (Box 170)
  - Student Health Budgets (1 of 2), 1970 September-1991 March (Box 170)
  - Student Health Budgets (2 of 2), 1970 September-1991 March (Box 171)
  - Student Health Immunization: Measles, 1989 (Box 171)
  - Student Health Service Correspondence, 1986 March-1991 October; 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Student Health: Student Problems, 1973-1991 June (Box 200)
  - Student Health Service Health Educator, 1985-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 171)
  - Student Life, Office Of, 1982-1990 (Box 171)
  - Students' Personal Problems, 1984-1991 June (Box 200)
  - Student Privacy: Policy, 1970-1984 (Box 172)
  - Student Projects, 1986-1991 June (Box 172)
  - Study Abroad Programs, 1989 April-1990 September (Box 172)
  - Summer. Session Plans, 1981 May-1989 October (Box 172)
  - Symposia, 1970-1985 (Box 172)
  - Teacher Course Evaluation, 1971-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 172)
  - Technical Services, Office Of, 1980-1991 June (Box 172)
  - Tel-com/telephones, 1986-1991 June (Box 172)
  - Theater Facilities Users Committee, 1982-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 173)
  - Tobacco Road, 1978-1983 (Box 173)
  - Transfer Students, 1974-1986 (Box 173)
  - Travel Service, 1979-1990 (Box 173)
  - Trinity College Board Of Visitors, 1988-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 173)
  - Trinity College Dean, Office Of, 1981-1991 February; 2 folders (Box 174)
  - Trustees Of Duke University, 1974-1991 May (Box 200)
    Board of Trustees restriction until 2041.
  - Undergraduate Admissions Tuition, 1990-1991 June (Box 174)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Tuition, 1969-1987 (Box 174)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, Council on, 1989-1991 June; 3 folders (Box 174)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board Correspondence, 1986-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 175)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board Correspondence, 1987, 1990 (Box 201)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board: Dean's Decisions, 1987-1990 June (Box 201)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board: Dean's Decisions, 1986-1987 June (Box 201)
  - Undergraduate Publications Board Correspondence, 1982-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 175)
  - Undergraduate: Publications Constitution, 1970-1991 June (Box 175)
  - Undergraduate Publication By-laws, 1970-1981 April (Box 175)
  - Undergraduate Publications Finance Committee, 1970-1991 June; 2 folders (Box 175)
    Copyright certificates
  - Undergraduate Education, 1983 February-1990 August (Box 176)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council, 1979 April-1988 October (Box 176)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council Agenda And Minutes, 1985 January-1985 February (Box 176)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council List Of Committees, 1976-1981 (Box 176)
  - United Fund, 1981-1989 (Box 176)
  - University Architect, 1981-1988 (Box 176)
  - University Bylaws, 1961 (Box 176)
  - University Counsel, 1981-1991 June (Box 176)
  - University Counsel, 1984-1985
  - University Judicial Board, 1978-1991 June (Box 201)
  - University Relations, 1981-1991 June (Box 176)
  - University Schedule, 1981-1991 June (Box 176)
  - University Secretary, 1982-1991 June (Box 176)
  - University Union (1 of 2), 1972-1991 June (Box 176)
  - University Union (2 of 2), 1972-1991 June (Box 177)
  - University Union: Arts & Crafts Workshop, 1982-1990 June (Box 177)
  - University Union: Board, 1981-1991 June (Box 177)
  - University Union: Constitution, 1975-1988 (Box 177)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1986-1991 June (Box 177)
  - University Union: Executive Committee, 1981-1985 June (Box 177)
  - University Union: Facilities Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 177)
  - University Union: Finance Committee, 1981-1991 June (Box 178)
  - University Union: Graphic Arts, 1980-1991 (Box 178)
  - University Union: Major Attractions, 1976-1990 (Box 178)
  - University Union: Major Attractions, 1982 (Box 201)
  - University Union: Major Speakers, 1981-1991 June (Box 178)
  - University Union: Performing Arts, 1981-1991 June (Box 178)
  - Urban Land Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 178)
  - Use Of University Facilities, 1982-1987 (Box 178)
  - Women's Studies, 1986-1991 January; 2 folders (Box 179)
  - WXDU-FM, 1983-1991 June (Box 179)
  - WXDU: Radio Station (License Permit), 1983-1992; 3 folders (Box 179)
  - WXDU: Radio Station (License Permit), 1982-1983 (Box 180)
  - DU Radio Board, 1980-1991 (Box 180)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1983-1990 June (Box 180)
  - Excuses: Students, 1980 February-1991 October
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 180)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 180)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 180)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 181)
  - President's Council On Black Affairs: Minutes, 1976 January-1976 May (Box 181)
- Accession A94-11, 12
  The materials in this series were created or collected by Maureen Cullins, Assistant to the Vice President of Student Affairs during the early 1990s. The series includes correspondence, notes, planning documents, budgets, reports, and other materials related to the Black on White Symposium (a symposium on the experience of black students and faculty at primarily white institutions such as Duke University) and the Richard Whitted Institute (a summer program for black students in North Carolina held at Duke). Materials are arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - Black on White (1 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box 181)
  - Black on White (2-3 of 3), 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Advertisements, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Clippings, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Final Report Draft 3, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Final Report, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Follow-up, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Black on White: Participants' Travel and Accommodations, 1989 (Box 182)
  - Richard Whitted Institute, 1988; 2 folders (Box 183)
  - Richard Whitted Institute, 1989; 3 folders (Box 183)
  - Richard Whitted Institute (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 183)
  - Richard Whitted Institute (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 184)
  - Richard Whitted Institute, 1991; 2 folders (Box 184)
  - Richard Whitted Institute, 1992 (Box 184)
- Accession A95-112, 13
  This series includes materials on the Student Affairs Committee of the Board of Trustees, of which William Griffith was a member. Contents include minutes, agendas, correspondence, and supplementary materials given to the Committee.
  Additional materials in this accession that were materials from general Board of Trustees meetings were removed and discarded; those materials duplicated materials found in the Board of Trustees Records.
  Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee Correspondence, September 1989 - April 1992; 4 folders (Box 202)
    Board of Trustee records are restricted until 2042
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee Correspondence, April 1984-June 1989; 5 folders (Box 203)
    Board of Trustee records are restricted until 2039
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee Correspondence, December 1980-September 1984; 5 folders (Box 204)
    Board of Trustee records are restricted until 2034
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Committee Membership, 1980-1990 (Box 205)
    Board of Trustee records are restricted until 2040
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Committee Minutes, September 1982-April 1992; 4 folders (Box 205)
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Committee Minutes, December 1980-September 1982 (Box 206)
    Board of Trustee records are restricted until 2032
- Accession A96-25, 14
  This series includes materials primarily related to the functioning of the Student Affairs office, including staff meeting minutes, agendas, correspondence, and budget planning materials. This series includes materials from both William Griffith's and Janet Dickerson's time as Vice President for Student Affairs.
  - Student Affairs Staff, 1979-1990 (Box 184)
  - Student Affairs Staff Agenda, April 1989-September 1991 (Box 184)
  - Student Affairs Staff Agenda, 1986 September-1989 March (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs Staff Correspondence, 1986 December-1991 April; 3 folders (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs Staff Minutes, 1986 September-1991 April; 2 folders (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs/Academic Deans Retreat, 1992 January (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs/Auxilliaries Offsite, 1991 October (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs Other Universities, 1987-1991 (Box 185)
  - Student Affairs Other Universities, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs: Cornell University, 1984-1987 (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs: NCSU, 1980, 1991 (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs: Rice University, 1979, 1984 (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs: Stanford University, 1981, 1989 (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs: UNC-CH, 1972-1982 (Box 186)
  - Student Affairs Staff Retreat, 1992 June 19 (Box 187)
  - Budget, Planning, and Analysis, 1980-1995; 5 folders (Box 187)
    Administrative records are restricted until 2020
    File contents are not chronological
- Accession UA2018-0084, circa 2010s; 3 Linear Feet
  Accession UA2018-0084 contains materials from Larry Moneta's time as Vice Provost for Student Affairs, circa 2010s.
  Access restricted. Collection contains administrative records less than 25 years old. Contact University Archives for access.
  - Athletic Department, 2 folders (Box 207)
  - A Miscellaneous (Box 207)
  - AAC&U (Box 207)
  - Alcohol (Box 207)
  - Alumni Affairs (Box 207)
  - American Council on Education (Box 207)
  - Archives (Box 207)
  - Art Museum (Box 207)
  - B Miscellaneous (Box 207)
  - Bath, Raheem (Box 207)
    CLOSED: FERPA
  - Beaufort Marine Lab (Box 207)
  - Bonfire Safety Program (Box 207)
  - BNCHMARK (Box 207)
  - Richard Brodhead (Box 207)
  - CAPS (Box 207)
  - CAPS Assess (Box 207)
  - C Miscellaneous (Box 207)
  - Campus Culture Initiative, 4 folders (Box 207)
  - Career Center (Box 207)
  - Central Campus Planning (Box 207)
  - Duke Chapel (Box 207)
  - The Chronicle (Box 207)
  - Clark, Charlotte (Box 207)
    Personnel records restriction.
  - COLE (Box 207)
  - Community Service Center (Box 207)
  - Samuel DuBois Cook Society (Box 207)
  - Council on Civic Engagement (Box 207)
  - CAPS (Box 207)
  - D Miscellaneous (Box 207)
  - Duke Dining (Box 207)
  - DPAC (Box 207)
  - Duke Durham Neighborhood Partnership (Box 207)
  - Duke Engage (Box 207)
  - Duke Student Government (DSG) (Box 207)
  - Duke Reach (Box 207)
  - Duke University Union (DUU) (Box 207)
  - DukeWeb (Box 207)
  - E Miscellaneous (Box 207)
  - Edens Mold (Box 207)
  - Emergency, Campus (Box 207)
  - Emergency/Safety (Box 207)
  - Faculty in Residence (Box 207)
  - FERPA (Box 207)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 207)
  - Fraternities (Box 207)
  - Endowments, 1 folder and bound notebook (Box 207)
  - F Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Freeman Center for Jewish Life, 2 folders (Box 208)
  - G Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Gates, Melinda (Box 208)
    RESTRICTED: Contains donor information.
  - Gattis Street Drugs and Rape Case (Box 208)
  - Graduate and Professional Student Council (GPSC) (Box 208)
  - H Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Heinz, Austen (Box 208)
    CLOSED: FERPA materials
  - I Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - IPC (Box 208)
  - J Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - K Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Lacrosse, 2006 (Box 208)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Matters, 1998 (Box 208)
  - LOCUS (Box 208)
    Restricted: Legal materials.
  - L Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - M Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Mahato, Abhijit (Box 208)
  - N Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - NCAA Recertification (Box 208)
  - O Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - Office of Student Activities and Facilities (OSAF) (Box 208)
  - Miscellaneous P (Box 208)
  - Parents Correspondence? (Box 208)
  - R Miscellaneous (Box 208)
  - President Correspondence (Box 208)
  - PSM Correspondence (Box 208)
  - Recommendation Letters A-Z (Box 209)
  - Residential Housing (Box 209)
  - Residential (Box 209)
  - Robertson Scholars (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous S (Box 209)
  - Student Run Business (Box 209)
  - SAE/DSP Fraternity (Box 209)
  - SALAP (Box 209)
  - Smart House (Box 209)
  - STR P' - N 09, 2009 (Box 209)
  - Student Administrative Services Steering Committee (Box 209)
  - Student Correspondence A-Z (Box 209)
  - Student Centers (Box 209)
  - Student Funding Task Force (SFTF) (Box 209)
  - Student Health, 2 folders (Box 209)
  - Student Health Center (Box 209)
  - SHS Study (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous T (Box 209)
  - Trinity Park Residents (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous U (Box 209)
  - UHCSR Brochure and Master Policy, 2009 October 29 (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous V (Box 209)
  - VA Tech (Box 209)
  - Voter Registration (Box 209)
  - Miscellaneous W (Box 209)
- Unprocessed accession A72-43
  Accession A72-43: Materials from Herbert Herring's time as Vice President for Student Affairs, prior to 1965; boxes original 1-6.